mobileseva.in 2015-04-29

# Private Policy - MovileSeva.in

**Security**

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. 

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

We collect personally identifiable information (email address) from you when you set up a free account with MobileSeva.in. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as searching for properties, viewing property contact information, and registering a property) do require registration.

We do use your contact information to send you offers as well as results of your search. You may always opt-out of receiving such information; see the _Choice/Opt-Out_ section below

**Opt-out**

mobileseva.in provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

To remove your contact information from all MobileSeva.in lists and newsletters, Please contact us at the address below.

**Sharing Personnel Information**

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

mobileseva.in and its affiliates will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.

**Links to Other Sites**

Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. mobileseva.in is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address:

**OSS** **Retails Private Limited,**  
102, 103, Chawda Commercial Complex,  
Behind Chincholi Bunder Fire Station,  
New Link Road, Mindspace,  
Malad West, Mumbai 400 064.

Tel : **022 4208 4208**  
Email : [**info@onestopshop.in**](mailto:info@onestopshop.in)
